<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Garpun_partners on Devision Support</title>
    <link>https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Garpun_partners on Devision Support</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ru-ru</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 12:59:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to connect to the program</title>
      <link>https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/answer/15mk0sg5k3vqg4iegm-kq1qdpjw5zqcdb.en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 12:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/answer/15mk0sg5k3vqg4iegm-kq1qdpjw5zqcdb.en/</guid>
      <description>Important! The participation of a client account under GCS begins only from the moment of CORRECT LINK to MCC Garpun. BOTH conditions must be followed - binding by first link and admin rights.
1. Partner account must be under Garpun Tools 613-754-8619  If you do not already have an account, create a ticket in partners.garpun.com and technical support staff will be able to create it for you. If you already have your own account, you need to establish a connection with MCC we request access to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to properly link your Google Ads account to MCC Garpun</title>
      <link>https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/answer/1a9atrarwyozuqgz0sg8z3mxxwtnughib.en/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 12:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/answer/1a9atrarwyozuqgz0sg8z3mxxwtnughib.en/</guid>
      <description>Accept the invitation from the letter in the mail or in the account http://ads.google.com Set the &amp;ldquo;Admin&amp;rdquo; option for the Garpun Tools 613-754-8619 manager in the Google Ads interface Verify that the first manager has the Garpun Tools 613-754-8619 manager installed.  An example of the correct connection:
Have a question? Contact technical support: support@garpun.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Как правильно привязать аккаунт Google Ads к MCC Garpun</title>
      <link>https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/answer/1a9atrarwyozuqgz0sg8z3mxxwtnughib/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 05:23:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/answer/1a9atrarwyozuqgz0sg8z3mxxwtnughib/</guid>
      <description>Примите приглашение из письма в почте или в аккаунте http://ads.google.com Установите опцию «Администратор» для менеджера Garpun Tools 613-754-8619 в интерфейсе Google Ads Проверьте, что первым менеджером установлен менеджер Garpun Tools 613-754-8619.  Пример правильной связи:
Подробнее в разделе помощь. Возникли вопросы? Обратитесь в службу технической поддержки: support@garpun.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Как подключиться к программе</title>
      <link>https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/answer/15mk0sg5k3vqg4iegm-kq1qdpjw5zqcdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 16:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://support.devision.io/garpun_partners/answer/15mk0sg5k3vqg4iegm-kq1qdpjw5zqcdb/</guid>
      <description>Важно! Участие аккаунта клиента под GCS начинается только с момента КОРРЕКТНОЙ ПРИВЯЗКИ к MCC Garpun. Должны быть соблюдены ОБА условия - привязка первым линком и админские права.
1. Аккаунт партнера должен быть под Garpun Tools 613-754-8619  Если у Вас еще нет аккаунта - создайте тикет в partners.garpun.com и сотрудники технической поддержки смогут создать его для Вас Если у Вас уже есть свой аккаунт, то необходимо установить связь с MCC запрашиваем к нему доступ Необходимо, добавить Garpun Tools 613-754-8619 как главного менеджера.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>